bankwithunited.com 2016-03-15

# FACTS

                                                                                                                                            Rev. 12/2015
                               WHAT DOES UNITED DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
FACTS
Why?                           Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers
                               the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect,
                               share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we
                               do.
What?                          The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with
                               us. This information can include:
                                 ● Social Security number and Payment history
                                 ● Credit history and Transaction history
                                 ● Account transactions and Account balances
How?                           All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business.
                               In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal
                               information; the reasons United chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
     Reasons we can share your personal information                              Does United share?                    Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes –                                                         Yes                                  No
such as to process your transactions, maintain your
account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes –                                                                 Yes                                  Yes
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                                           Yes                                  No
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes –                                             Yes                                  No
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes –                                              No                             We don’t share
information about your creditworthiness
For our affiliates to market to you                                                          Yes                                  Yes
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                                            No                             We don’t share
To limit our                    Call Toll-free 1.800.327.9862 to speak to one of our Customer Service Representatives
sharing                         Call or visit one of our branch locations and speak to one of our staff members
                                Please note:
                                If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 45 days from the date we provide
                                this notice at account opening. When you are no longer our customer, we may continue to share your
                                information as described in this notice.
                                However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?                     Call toll-free 1.800.327.9862 or go to www.bankwithunited.com
Privacy Model Disclosure                                                                                                              PRIV-MODEL 8/1/2010
VMP® Bankers Systems™
Wolters Kluwer Financial Services © 2010                                     2012.1/1847 200158149-010 Custom EPRV1847                        Page 1 of 2

Page 2
Who We Are
Who is providing this notice?           United means the following institutions: United Bank, Inc., United Bank, United
                                        Brokerage Services, Inc., United Title Company, and United Bankshares, Inc.
What We Do
How does United protect my              To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use
personal information?                   security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer
                                        safeguards and secured files and buildings.
                                        We also maintain other physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect this
                                        information and we limit access to information to those employees for whom access
                                        is appropriate.
How does United collect my              We collect your personal information, for example, when you
personal information?                     ● Apply for a loan                     ● Give us your employment history
                                          ● Give us your income information ● Give us your wage statements
                                          ● Provide employment information
                                        We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus,
                                        affiliates, or other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing?          Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                          ● sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your
                                              creditworthiness
                                          ● affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                          ● sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                        State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
                                        See below for more on your rights under state law.
What happens when I limit               Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
sharing for an account I hold
jointly with someone else?
Definitions
Affiliates                              Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-
                                        financial companies.
                                           Our affiliates include financial companies such as: United Bank, Inc., United
                                              Bank, United Brokerage Services, Inc., and United Title Company.
Nonaffiliates                           Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                        non-financial companies.
                                          ● United does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint Marketing                         A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market
                                        financial products or services to you.
                                        ● Our joint marketing partners include identity theft protection, financial products
                                            or services and investment/insurance companies.
Other Important Information
For Alaska, Illinois, Maryland and North Dakota Customers. We will not share personal information with nonaffiliates
either for them to market to you or for joint marketing - without your authorization.
For California Customers. We will not share personal information with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or
for joint marketing - without your authorization. We will also limit our sharing of personal information about you with our
affiliates to comply with all California privacy laws that apply to us.
For Massachusetts, Mississippi and New Jersey Customers. We will not share personal information from deposit or
share relationships with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint marketing - without your authorization.
For Vermont Customers. We will not share personal information with nonaffiliates for them to market to you without
your authorization and we will not share personal information with affiliates or for joint marketing about your
creditworthiness without your authorization.
